A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, International Relations, RG 1.3, Series 155 FA388A
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Relations, 1971-1989; 155
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia, 1984 June 6 (Box 15, Folder 161)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia, 1984 June 6 (Box 15, Folder 162)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia, 1984 June 6 (Box 15, Folder 163)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia, 1984 June 6 (Box 15, Folder 164)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia, 1984 June 12-13 (Box 15, Folder 165)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia, 1984 September-December (Box 15, Folder 166)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia, 1985 January-March (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia, 1985 December (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (I), 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 171)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (II), 1981 (Box 16, Folder 172)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (III), 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 173)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (IV), 1982 July-October (Box 16, Folder 174)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (V), 1982 November (Box 16, Folder 175)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (VI), 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 176)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (VII), 1984 (Box 16, Folder 177)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (VIII), 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 178)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (IX), 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 179)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (X), 1985 March 4 (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XI), 1985 March 4 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XII), 1985 March 4 (Box 16, Folder 182)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XIII), 1985 March 4 (Box 16, Folder 183)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XIV): Appendix B (I), 1987 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 184)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XV): Appendix B (II), 1987 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 185)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XVI): Appendix B (III), 1987 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 186)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XVII): Appendix B (IV), 1987 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 187)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XVIII): Appendix C (I), 1987 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 188)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XIX): Appendix C (II), 1987 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 189)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XX): Appendix D (I), 1987 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 190)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XXI): Appendix D (II), 1987 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 191)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XXII): Appendix D (III), 1987 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 192)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XXIII): Appendix D (IV), 1987 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 193)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XXIV): Appendix E (I), 1987 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 194)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XXV): Appendix E (II), 1987 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XXVI): Appendix E (III), 1987 February 2 (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XXVII): Appendix E (IV), 1987 February 2 (Box 18, Folder 197)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XXVIII): Appendix E (V), 1987 February 2 (Box 18, Folder 198)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XXIX): Appendix F, 1987 February 2 (Box 18, Folder 199)
  - Asia Society: China Council and Asia: Supplementary Material (XXX): Appendix G-H, 1987 February 2 (Box 18, Folder 200)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 201)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1975 January-September (Box 18, Folder 202)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1975 October-1976 February (Box 18, Folder 203)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1976 March-June (Box 18, Folder 204)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1976 July-August (Box 18, Folder 205)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1976 November-1977 (Box 18, Folder 206)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1978 February-August (Box 18, Folder 207)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1978 October-December (Box 18, Folder 208)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1979 January-July (Box 19, Folder 209)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1979 August-December (Box 19, Folder 210)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 211)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 212)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1983 January-July (Box 19, Folder 213)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1983 August (Box 19, Folder 214)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1983 September-December (Box 19, Folder 215)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1984 April-July (Box 19, Folder 216)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1984 August-October (Box 19, Folder 217)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1984 November-December (Box 19, Folder 218)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 219)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 220)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control: Supplementary Material (I), 1974-1975, no date (Box 20, Folder 221)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control: Supplementary Material (II), 1975 August (Box 20, Folder 222)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control: Supplementary Material (III), 1975 September-October (Box 20, Folder 223)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control: Supplementary Material (IV), 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 224)
  - Aspen Institute: Arms Control: Supplementary Material (V), 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 225)
  - Aspen Institute: Leadership Conference, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 226)
  - Aspen Institute: Leadership Conference, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 227)
  - Association of Former Members of Congress: International Fellows, 1983 June-September (Box 20, Folder 228)
  - Association of Former Members of Congress: International Fellows, 1983 October-November (Box 20, Folder 229)
  - Association of Former Members of Congress: International Fellows, 1984 March-May (Box 20, Folder 230)
  - Association of Former Members of Congress: International Fellows, 1984 October-November (Box 20, Folder 231)
  - Association of Former Members of Congress: International Fellows, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 232)
  - Association of Former Members of Congress: International Fellows, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 233)
  - Association of Former Members of Congress: International Fellows: Supplementary Material, 1974, 1983-1985, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 234)
  - Atlantic Council: Asian Security, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 235)
  - Atlantic Council: Asian Security, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 236)
  - Atlantic Council: Asian Security, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 237)
  - Atlantic Council: Asian Security, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 238)
  - Atlantic Council: Presidency and Congress in Foreign Policy, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 239)
  - Atlantic Council: Presidency and Congress in Foreign Policy, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 240)
  - Atlantic Council: Presidency and Congress in Foreign Policy: Supplementary Material (I), 1984 February 1 (Box 21, Folder 241)
  - Atlantic Council: Presidency and Congress in Foreign Policy: Supplementary Material (II), 1984 February 1 (Box 22, Folder 242)
  - Atlantic Council: Presidency and Congress in Foreign Policy: Supplementary Material (III), 1984 February 1 (Box 22, Folder 243)
  - Atlantic Council: Presidency and Congress in Foreign Policy: Supplementary Material (IV), 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 244)
  - Atlantic Council: Energy and Global Security, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 245)
  - Atlantic Council: Energy and Global Security, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 246)
  - Atlantic Council: Southern Peripherals: Front of File Material, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 247)
  - Atlantic Council: Southern Peripherals, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 248)
  - Atlantic Council: Southern Peripherals, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 249)
  - Atlantic Council: Southern Peripherals, 1985-1988 (Box 22, Folder 250)
  - Meron Benvenisti, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 251)
  - Meron Benvenisti, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 252)
  - Meron Benvenisti, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 253)
  - Meron Benvenisti, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 254)
  - Meron Benvenisti, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 255)
  - Meron Benvenisti: Supplementary Material (I): "The West Bank and Gaza Data Base Project Pilot Study Report", pp. 1-67, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 256)
  - Meron Benvenisti: Supplementary Material (II): "The West Bank and Gaza Data Base Project Pilot Study Report", pp. 68-129, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 257)
  - Meron Benvenisti: Supplementary Material (III), 1982 (Box 23, Folder 258)
  - Meron Benvenisti: Supplementary Material (IV), 1983 April (Box 23, Folder 259)
  - Meron Benvenisti: Supplementary Material (V), 1983 July 19 (Box 23, Folder 260)
  - Meron Benvenisti: Supplementary Material (VI), 1983 July 19 (Box 23, Folder 261)
  - Meron Benvenisti: Supplementary Material (VII), 1983 July 19 (Box 23, Folder 262)
  - Meron Benvenisti: Supplementary Material (VIII), 1983 July 19 (Box 23, Folder 263)
  - Meron Benvenisti: Supplementary Material (IX), 1984, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 264)
  - (489) – Black Lawyers' Association: Legal Education Centre: Modise Khoza, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 265)
  - (489) – Black Lawyers' Association: Legal Education Centre: Modise Khoza, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 266)
  - (489) – Black Lawyers' Association: Legal Education Centre: Modise Khoza, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 267)
  - (489) – Black Lawyers' Association: Legal Education Centre: Modise Khoza, 1987-1988, 1990, no date (Box 24, Folder 268)
  - Brookings Institution: Chinese Conferences, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 269)
  - Brookings Institution: Chinese Conferences, 1981-1982, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 270)
  - Brookings Institution: Chinese Conferences: Supplementary Material (I), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 271)
  - Brookings Institution: Chinese Conferences: Supplementary Material (II), 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 272)
  - Brookings Institution: Chinese Conferences: Supplementary Material (III), 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 273)
  - Brookings Institution: Chinese Conferences: Supplementary Material (IV), 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 274)
  - Brookings Institution: Chinese Conferences: Supplementary Material (V), 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 275)
  - Brookings Institution: Chinese Conferences: Supplementary Material (VI), 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 276)
  - Brookings Institution: Chinese Conferences: Supplementary Material (VII), 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 277)
  - Brookings Institution: Economies of the Advanced Developing Countries, 1977-1981 (Box 24, Folder 278)
  - Brookings Institution: Economies of the Advanced Developing Countries, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 279)
  - Brookings Institution: Energy Policy History, 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 280)
  - Brookings Institution: Energy Policy History: Evaluation, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 281)
  - Brookings Institution: Food Supply and Demand, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 282)
  - Brookings Institution: Food Supply and Demand, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 283)
  - Brookings Institution: Food Supply and Demand: Evaluation, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 284)
  - Brookings Institution: International Economic and Security Policy, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 285)
  - Brookings Institution: International Economic and Security Policy, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 286)
  - Brookings Institution: International Economic and Security Policy, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 287)
  - Brookings Institution: International Economic and Security Policy, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 288)
  - Brookings Institution: Middle East Program: Front of File Material, 1984-1986 (Box 25, Folder 289)
  - Brookings Institution: Middle East Program, 1984 January-September (Box 25, Folder 290)
  - Brookings Institution: Middle East Program, 1984 November-1986, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 291)
  - Brookings Institution: World Bank Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 292)
  - Brookings Institution: World Inflation (I), 1975, 1977-1980 (Box 26, Folder 293)
  - Brookings Institution: World Inflation (II), 1974-1975 July (Box 26, Folder 294)
  - Brookings Institution: World Inflation (II), 1975 August (Box 26, Folder 295)
  - Brookings Institution: World Inflation (II), 1975 September-1977 April (Box 26, Folder 296)
  - Brookings Institution: World Inflation (II), 1977 September-1980 (Box 26, Folder 297)
  - Brookings Institution: Year 2000 and International Security, 1976 April-June (Box 26, Folder 298)
  - Brookings Institution: Year 2000 and International Security, 1976 July-1979, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 299)
  - California State University: Mexico-United States Conference, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 300)
  - California State University: Mexico-United States Conference, 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 301)
  - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc.: U. S.-Brazilian Commission, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 302)
  - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc.: U. S.-Brazilian Commission, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 303)
  - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc.: U. S.-Brazilian Commission, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 304)
  - Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc.: U. S.-Brazilian Commission, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 305)
  - Center of Research and Economics Teaching (Mexico): International Politics, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 306)
  - Center of Research and Economics Teaching: International Politics, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 307)
  - Center of Research and Economics Teaching: International Politics, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 308)
  - Center of Research and Economics Teaching: International Politics, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 309)
  - Center of Research and Economics Teaching: International Politics: Supplementary Material (I), 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 310)
  - Center of Research and Economics Teaching: International Politics: Supplementary Material (II), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 311)
  - Centre for Economic Policy Research, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 312)
  - Centre for Economic Policy Research, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 313)
  - Centre for Economic Policy Research, 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 314)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 315)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 316)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology, 1984 March-April (Box 28, Folder 317)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology, 1984 October (Box 28, Folder 318)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology, 1984 November-1985 July (Box 28, Folder 319)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology, 1985 December-1986 (Box 28, Folder 320)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology, 1987, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 321)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology: Supplementary Material (I), 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 322)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology: Supplementary Material (II), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 323)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology: Supplementary Material (III): CEPS Papers, Nos. 1-17, 22, 25-26, 28-30, 32 (20 pieces), 1983-1987 (Box 29, Folder 324)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology: Supplementary Material (IV): CEPS Working Documents (Economic), Nos. 1-3, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 325)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology: Supplementary Material (V): CEPS Working Documents (Economic), Nos. 4-6, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 326)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology: Supplementary Material (VI): CEPS Working Documents (Economic), Nos. 7-9, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 327)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology: Supplementary Material (VII): CEPS Working Documents (Economic), Nos. 10, 12-13, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 328)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology: Supplementary Material (VIII): CEPS Working Documents (Economic), Nos. 13-14, 18, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 329)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology: Supplementary Material (IX): CEPS Working Documents (Economic), Nos. 24-25, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 330)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology: Supplementary Material (X): CEPS Working Documents (Economic), Nos. 26-27, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 331)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology: Supplementary Material (XI): CEPS Working Documents (Political), Nos. 1-3, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 332)
  - Centre for European Policy Studies: High Technology: Supplementary Material (XII): CEPS Working Documents (Political), Nos. 4-5, 7, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 333)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States: Nigeria Trade and Investment, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 334)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (I), 1975, 1977-1978, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 335)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1974-1975 March (Box 31, Folder 336)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1975 April (Box 31, Folder 337)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1975 May-December (Box 31, Folder 338)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1976 March (Box 31, Folder 339)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1976 April-June (Box 31, Folder 340)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1976 July-August (Box 31, Folder 341)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1976 September-October (Box 31, Folder 342)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1976 November 1-12 (Box 31, Folder 343)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1976 November 15-December (Box 31, Folder 344)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1977 January-March (Box 31, Folder 345)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1977 April-June (Box 31, Folder 346)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1977 July-September (Box 31, Folder 347)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1977 October (Box 32, Folder 348)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1977 November (Box 32, Folder 349)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1977 December (Box 32, Folder 350)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1978 January-April (Box 32, Folder 351)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1978 May (Box 32, Folder 352)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1978 July (Box 32, Folder 353)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1978 August-December (Box 32, Folder 354)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1979 (Box 32, Folder 355)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1980 January-February (Box 32, Folder 356)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1980 March-July (Box 32, Folder 357)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring (II), 1980 September-1982 (Box 32, Folder 358)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Evaluation, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 359)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material (I), 1974, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 360)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material (II), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 361)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Dose-Commitment Model Workshop (I), 1977 July (Box 33, Folder 362)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material (III), 1978 (Box 33, Folder 363)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Dose-Commitment Model Workshop (II), 1977 July (Box 3, Folder 364)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Dose-Commitment Model Workshop (III), 1977 July (Box 33, Folder 365)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Dose-Commitment Model Workshop (IV), 1977 July (Box 33, Folder 366)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Dose-Commitment Model Workshop (V), 1977 July (Box 33, Folder 367)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Dose-Commitment Model Workshop (VI), 1977 July (Box 33, Folder 368)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Dose-Commitment Model Workshop (VII), 1977 July (Box 33, Folder 369)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Evaluation Workshop (I), 1976 September (Box 33, Folder 370)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Evaluation Workshop (II), 1976 September (Box 33, Folder 371)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Evaluation Workshop (III), 1976 September (Box 33, Folder 372)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Evaluation Workshop (IV), 1976 September (Box 33, Folder 373)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Evaluation Workshop (V), 1976 September (Box 33, Folder 374)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Evaluation Workshop (VI), 1976 September (Box 33, Folder 375)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Evaluation Workshop (VII), 1976 September (Box 33, Folder 376)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Reports (I): Report No. 11, 1979, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 377)
  - Chelsea College: Global Monitoring: Supplementary Material/MARC Reports (II): Report Nos. 1-7, 9-10, 12-25 (22 pieces), 1976-1981 (Box 34, Folder 378)
  - Chicago Council on Foreign Relations: Spain and Portugal Democratization, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 379)
  - Chicago Council on Foreign Relations: Spain and Portugal Democratization, 1984, 1986, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 380)
  - Chinese Foreign Policy: Conference, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 381)
  - Chulalongkorn University: Security Studies, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 382)
  - Chulalongkorn University: Security Studies, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 383)
  - Chulalongkorn University: Security Studies, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 384)
  - Chulalongkorn University: Security Studies: Supplementary Material, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 385)
  - Citizens for Ocean Law: Seminars, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 386)
  - Citizens for Ocean Law: Seminars, 1983 January-October (Box 35, Folder 387)
  - Citizens for Ocean Law: Seminars, 1983 December-1985 (Box 35, Folder 388)
  - City University of New York: Middle East Conference, 1982-1985 (Box 35, Folder 389)
  - Columbia University: American Sovietologists in South Africa, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 390)
  - Columbia University: Defense Planning, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 391)
  - Columbia University: Defense Planning, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 392)
  - Columbia University: Defense Planning, 1981-1984 (Box 36, Folder 393)
  - Columbia University: Boris Rabbot, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 394)
  - Columbia University: Boris Rabbot, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 395)
  - Columbia University: Boris Rabbot: Evaluation, 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 396)
  - Columbia University: Trade Policy Conference, 1983-1985 (Box 36, Folder 397)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy, 1975 March-April (Box 36, Folder 398)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy, 1975 May-August (Box 36, Folder 399)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy, 1975 September-1977 (Box 36, Folder 400)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 401)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 402)